Hello friends, today our Nifty
50 closed 16 points positive
.  I was expecting it to be as good as the
bull trend that was there yesterday,
but it was
n't as good as that.  If you look closely, you'll see that it's a small,
positive moment
.  If you look at it in the morning, it won't
rise to a large extent.  It
was a one-way market, both going up and down the hill.  If you look at it, it's almost
20-30 points down, but if
you look at it again, it's
a mixed trading, saying that it's worth 20-30 points positive, and so on.
If you look at the final, it's a
good positive momentum for now
.  The Sensex
closed with a positive momentum of 63 points.
Similarly, if you look at the Bank Nifty, it
closed 162 points positive
.  If you look at the Nifty ID, it's
flat.  There is no
ups and downs.  If you
came here and looked at the pharmacy, it would have been a bit
negative.
If you look at all the pharma metals, they've gone a little on the negative side
.  This has brought
a positive momentum to the auto sector
.
If you look at the Nifty Energy FMCG media, it seems to have
closed in a very positive moment, almost 105 points.
If you look at mid-cap and small-cap, there is
no significant upside.  I would say it's almost 1%, or
even flat
.  Only 1% of the good ones are
close.  From morning, even in
a big field, there was a 10.23 range, but this was the only
positive side
.  Even the negative side did
n't go that far. It was just a matter of
mid-cap and small-cap.   No more
data is
coming today.  We'll see when it arrives.  If
you look at it from the perspective of most people, there are possibilities for the buying side to still exist today
.  Because Nethi was also a bit on the
buying side.  If
you look at it the same way,
there are possibilities that it still exists today.   If you
look at who was the top performer in the Nifty 50 today, it was Mahindra.   It closed with
a positive momentum of almost 2.17%
.   If
you look at the next ones, Wipro, SBI,
Mahindra, and NS, they are all
closing with a very positive momentum
.  Similarly, if you
look at who was in the top loser, it was Steram
Finance.   If
you look at it at around 2.35%, it's going to be on the negative side and it's going to be
closed.  Similarly,
if you look at Eternal Gold, you will see the negative side, and
if you look at Sun Pharma, Tata Steel, and Cipla, everything will have gone to a negative side
.
If you look at the Stera Finance report, it closed with a nice
positive momentum yesterday.   If
you look at it today, it's a negative
side.  If you look at everything, you'll see that it's just a
profit booking
.  So, it's just a mix
.  Let's wait and see.
If you look at the US market right now, it's not open yet.  But if you had
come and seen it yesterday, the Dow Jones would have closed with
a negative result
.  It has closed at a negative 436 points
.  Similarly,
the S&P 500 closed 24 points negative and the
Nasdaq 37 points positive
.  So when I came here, it was
a bit mixed up
.  I ca
n't say how this is today.
There are possibilities for it to be positive.  If you
look at the European market right now, it's in a very
positive momentum.
So look at the data, it's a 112 point
ADAC, 32 point CA, and 8 point
positive momentum.   The
Asian market has been a mixed bag
.  Nikkei
has gone negative by 14 points.  Aung San Suu Kyi is 72
points negative, come and see Taiwan is
220 points positive.  If
you look at our market, it has also
turned positive.  Taiwan is positive, but
only Hang Sung and Nikkei
are a little on the negative side.
Otherwise, nothing else.  So, if you've come and
seen this, you've probably just gotten a mix
.  If you're looking at the gold rate, there's been a
nice downfall today
.  It's down almost ₹45
.  22 karat gold.  ₹9100
is in that range.
If you look at it like that, come and see 24 karat gold,
is in that range.  It has
come down to almost ₹49.  Keep
thinking until the gold runs out
.  Whether
you're looking at silver, whether it's physical or digital, it's down by ₹1.   There
were 115 of them.  Today it is ₹14
.  If you look at the silver, it's all the same
.
If you look at the silver already, if
you look at a kilo, it's almost
1115 to
over 15,000.  If you look at Almost,
they say that 1220,000 people have come and reached it.
They say it will come soon and there are possibilities for around 1 lakh.
Keep considering the silver until it's all gone.  A long-term
portfolio would be a good investment
.  Next time, if you come and
see the SP, they will tell you if they are going to do a Kayabi. If you
come and see their floor price, they will
give you 811. They
gave a statement like this. They said that they will give you a price that is
almost 2.5% discount than the current market. They said that they will give you a
price like this. They didn't
say anything like that. I just saw it on a news money control
.  That was the news he had
received.  If you look at it like that, if
you look at L&T Tech, they would have said that this margin has increased to
almost
316 crores this quarter
.  If
you look at the revenue, they say it has increased by almost 16%
.  But
full details are yet to come.  I've looked for it in Manikander, but it
still hasn't come up.
I'll update the screener as soon as it arrives.  Similarly, if you look at FC Life, they have
said that the net premium has increased by a good 15% in this quarter. Year on year, if
you look at this 2024, it
was 12509 crores, but now it is
crores.  So if
you've seen that much, it's a great improvement
.  If you look at
the profit, it's a
good improvement of almost 14%
.  In the same year 2024, it
was 478 crores.  If you look now,
546 crores have come like that.
So, the profit has increased significantly
.   If
you also saw the premium, it would have been a great
improvement.  Similarly,
if you look at ICICI Bank's
net profit for the quarter, they would have
said that there was a good improvement of almost 28.7%.  If
you look at this, it
was 580 crores when it came to Iran in June last year.  If you come and
look now, it's 747 crores.  That's a
great improvement.  Similarly, if
you look at the total income, they say there has been a good improvement of almost 13.7%
.  If
you look at last year, it was 532 crores.
If you look now, it's 6083 crores
.  So, there's a good improvement
.  If you look at
everything, the life insurance company
has given a good result now.
Both HDFC and IC
have given good results.  Let's wait
a little and see how they give something like that
.  If
you had seen Zydus Life Insurance come next, US
FD would have come and given approval.  If you've seen this, the
US
FDA has approved the production of the Silicic Acid B capsule.
So if you come to Zydus Life Sciences and
see this, there is some good, positive news
.  If you look at the next example, Justile, if
you look at the revenue for this quarter, there has been a
good improvement of almost 6.42%, as
they say, year on year, last year it
was 280 crores.
If you look now, there are 298 krosa.
If you look at the net profit, they say that it's a good improvement of 13.47%
.
Come and see last year, there was a 141 Crosa.   If
you look at the June quarter, this quarter, this year, it's 160 crores.   There has been a
great improvement.  Similarly, if
you look at Geojet Financial Services, they said that revenue for the quarter was
down
.  They have said that it has gone down well to about 13.33%
.  It
only came in quarter and quarter and it went down well
.  Similarly,
if you look at the net profit, they say that the downball has
gone down well, up to about 11.63%
.  If
you look at it this same year, it
was 30.89 crores.  If you come and
see now, it's 27.29 crores.
If you look at the net profit,
you'll see that this is net profit year on year.  But if you
come to Revenue Town and see,
they would say that it's a good town, quarter by quarter.  Next, if
you look at Somani Ceramics, they have come and bought a 51%
stake.   I
bought a stake in a company called Beura Build Care. When
I looked at its value, I was told that it was 10 crores. When I looked at the
next one, I was told that it was going to be a rights issue. I was told that it was going to be done for about 400 crores. So, I think the information you gave is useful for everyone. See you in the next video with the next information.
Thank you friends.